The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world,
and to become the next Wizard King.
Even the parts of the Forsaken Realm
that were hardest hit by the enemy have begun to recover.
Things are finally looking brighter for the kingdom as a whole.
Yes, and to make this an everlasting peace rather than a fleeting one,
we all need to remain strong whatever comes our way.
Hope you're ready to work, sir.
We've got the captain's meeting as well as the decoration ceremony.
Your schedule is packed today.
Hmph.
So.
Just go.
What do you think?
How do you think?
Ticket's another story.
Some years, the same age.
You might have a victory.
Your pre-AF kids этом.
... feeling horrible
Shine like a demon
Denshin to
Akuuma ga
Kouzai shiteku
Seekai wa
Muzun darake sa
Omoi doori janaai
So no kurai de
Ageru yume wa dark side
So
Na do mo na do mo
Na do mo
Jouza o miyai de
Tuna geou
Nangai no no
Nichijou o tsuseme
Aijen ni hikare
You shine like a diamond
Why
Vigile
Dragons
People
They are
In un
In other Misomon
Nags
Our topic for today
Is who will participate in the Heart Kingdom's training?
The battle against the Spade Kingdom, which we promised Queen Lora Petyka we'd help with, is drawing near now
Of course, I know that you've all been making great strides on your own.
But we've just received word that they've completed preparations for their training regimen as well.
We've reached the final step.
There are five Spirit Guardians who will be working with us.
Each of them can only take a certain number of trainees.
As such, I'd like you all to tell me which subordinates you'll be nominating from each of your squads.
Now then, which of the Magic Knights are we sending?
Obviously, I pick Asta and Nero, especially since the Heart Kingdom already told us they wanted them.
Asta uses Anti-Magic, and Nero wields Forbidden Magic.
Not only that, but they're both at the Arcane Stage.
We know from experience that their unique abilities will be a tremendous asset in this fight.
And through further training, I'm sure they'll find ways to amplify their strengths even more.
They'll send Finral and Luck, too.
Oh, and Noelle, definitely.
Oh, what's wrong? Are you worried about her?
That's so sweet, you're such a protective big brother.
I feel like she and Luck would be a good complement to the others on account of their magic types.
Interestingly, one of the Spirit Guardians uses Lightning Spells, and the Queen has the Water Spirit known as Undine.
When you consider all of those factors, I believe your assessment is right on the money.
Besides, Luck's itching to go so badly, he can't stand it.
And it seems like Noelle's more motivated now than she's ever been.
That makes sense. Magicula is the devil who killed their mother, after all.
And as for Finral...
Well, he's just handy.
We can't underestimate the importance of support mages like him, especially if he improves his skill even more.
Perhaps he'll open up some new strategies for us.
Oh yeah, that's what I was gonna say.
From the Black Bulls, we have five mages.
Asta, Narrow, Luck Voltia, Noelle Silva, and the spatial mage called Finral.
Well, that's more than I expected.
That's cause I've got plenty of good people.
Should be a fairly strong lineup.
As for the Golden Dawn's nomination, I submit Mimosa for Million.
We are fighting a devil.
So I'm certain the conflict ahead will be brutal.
We can't hope to succeed without recovery mages.
Because she's a royal, she was born with great talent.
If we can help her to reach her full potential, then that bodes well for us.
A wise choice.
But is she your only nomination?
I hear the Wind Spirit Guardian is going to be involved, after all.
Actually, you know has declined.
Knowing him, I assume he had his reasons.
Hmm.
And who are the candidates from all the other squads?
From the Crimson Lion Kings, we have chosen Leopold Vermillion.
Leo's ambition is extremely high.
In fact, he asked our sister, Mera Leona, to help him train at the Volcano in the strong magic region.
Just thinking about that makes me tired.
No one in my squad can match Leo's passion and work ethic.
But he's still hesitant.
I'm hoping that this opportunity will ignite a flame within his heart that burns away that hesitation.
If he can overcome that, then not only will he be a powerful force in our battle against Spade,
but he can guard this kingdom with all the strength and pride of a great lion!
Excellent. I look forward to seeing how much Leo progresses, then.
What about the other squads?
Is there anyone you wish to nominate from the Blue Rose Knights?
First, sire, I would like you to clarify something for me.
Is it possible for one of the captains to nominate themselves?
Sure, that's alright.
Since you were possessed by an elf in the last conflict, I believe subjecting you to this training could provide some interesting results.
I still remember how it felt to have that elf spirit's power coursing through me.
Her red rose mana was far superior to my own.
It doesn't matter how I increase my strength, I just know that I must.
I'll do whatever it takes to experience that again.
And by experience, I meant the magic. Nothing more.
Then the only nominee from the Blue Rose Knights is Captain Charlotte herself, is that correct?
Yes.
Any other captains?
It troubles me to admit it, but I believe that younger candidates would be best.
I agree. And I'm quite capable of conducting my training on my own.
I'd be glad to go if it means I get to slash the Heart Kingdom open, ke-ke.
Yeah, you're not going.
I imagine this regimen will be grueling, but they'll discover and learn so much that they never would have been able to here in Clover.
They'll be in a brand new world. I expect them to take full advantage of that.
Discovering a new world?
My appetite's insatiable!
Keep being vigilant and training with your magic every day.
That would take protein.
Eat this! That's for the protein!
Each one of you has amazing potential. I'd like to see it grow even more.
Growing.
Yeah.
And this! That one's for the fat!
This is for the vitamins! This is for the fiber! This is for the collagen!
Me! Me! Me! Me! Me!
Oh my! Someone's full of energy!
Yeah, where the heck did that come from?
The only person I want to nominate from the Aqua Deer is me!
If I get stronger, then maybe that nice, beautiful lady will notice me.
We've probably selected enough candidates at this point.
But are there any others?
I don't have anyone from the Silver Eagles, but I assure you we'll train to the best of our ability and be ready for the fight against the Spade Kingdom.
As will we.
And we're going to handle things our way!
Well then, do we all agree on the candidates who were proposed?
As proved!
Lovely.
Lovely. I'm expecting great things from this group.
Sir!
Very well then. Today's captain's meeting is officially adjourned.
Good. That's finally over. See ya.
And just where do you think you're going?
The decoration ceremony is about to start.
Ugh. Do I really have to go to that?
But I got my wheels parked out front.
And my squad never gets picked.
We were told that all nine captains are required to be in attendance.
What? Why?
Well, you see, apparently the king himself is going to participate this time.
You're kidding me.
The captain's from every squad in one room. It's an all-star lineup.
I see they've required all the captains to attend since they knew I'd be making an appearance.
Exactly as it should be.
Up till now, the king's only seen me at a distance. He's bound to figure it out.
Captain Jack?
Will you let me come back to the squad?
What's with him?
Guess he needs me.
The slice into pieces!
I believe everyone is present now.
Then I say we start!
Hmm.
Attention all!
This is a special decoration ceremony for the Magic Knights who bravely fought against the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
The Wizard King is still unable to use his voice, so I'll be conducting this myself.
Without further ado...
For ado, Sol Merrin of the Blue Rose Knights with 21 stars. As of today, you'll be a 5th-class senior Magic Knight.
With your calm, quick thinking, you were able to transport the injured Wizard King to safety.
Please continue to exercise that wise judgment on the battlefield.
My, my. That young lady moved up three ranks at once.
She did save the Wizard King's life, so I'd say she's more than deserving of such a promotion.
To be honest, I wasn't calm at all.
Not to mention, Char had to be rescued by the Captain of the Black Bulls of all people.
Next time, I'll protect her without the help of some dumb, disgusting man!
Hmm?
Heads up.
Your subordinate's staring me down on something serious.
Is that so?
She's staring at Yami?
Oh no! Please, Sol! Don't tell me you like him as well!
Huh?
Wow, she looks so passionate!
Don't worry, Char, I won't let you down!
Next, with 23 stars.
The Golden Dawn's Mimosa Vermillion.
You're now a 2nd-class intermediate Magic Knight.
During the battle at the Shadow Palace, you showed great humanity while effectively fulfilling your duty as a recovery mage.
And we know that you'll save many more lives in the future.
If you ask me, Mimosa's the reason why so many more people understand the importance of recovery magic these days.
This is a great honor.
I'll do my best to live up to it during our battle with the Spade Kingdom.
And with a total of 18 stars, Leopold Vermillion of the Crimson Lion Kings, you are now a 4th-class Senior Magic Knight.
When the Captains were absent, you rallied your cohorts and did everything in your power to stop your Vice-Captain, who was possessed by an Elf.
I hope the strength of your character will continue to lead us down the path to victory.
It appears young Leopold is advanced by three ranks as well.
I'm sorry, I can't accept!
That night, if my brother hadn't shown up in time, we'd have all been annihilated!
It's true, I did everything I could, but it still wasn't good enough.
Everyone in my squad fought really hard to protect me, even at the risk of their own lives.
Truth is, I'm only a weakling!
I don't deserve this recognition!
You're a fool!
Have you no idea why they all put their lives on the line for your sake?
They were moved by your courage!
Your very existence inspired them to move forward!
They knew the future of our squad would be safe in your hands!
So accept the award!
It represents the tireless hope and resolve of the Crimson Lion King!
Hope and resolve?
Please forgive my hesitation!
I, Leopold Vermillion, will protect my squad and the kingdom from any foe, and become a mighty warrior who can lead the charge to victory!
And now you know, from the Golden Dawn, sir.
You've earned 77 stars total.
Amazing!
During the Star Festival for this year, did he just earn more than my whole squad?
You're being promoted as well, you know.
It's a first-class senior magic knight.
Huh?
This brat!
What?
You would award a title like that to a mere commoner?
You dealt a fatal blow to the Devil who was the source of all that destruction.
We're very proud of what you've achieved.
Thanks.
Now he's the same rank as Vice-Captain Longris!
I can't believe Yuno's already made it one step below the squad captains!
I don't really know what's going on, but it sounds pretty good!
Great job, Yuno!
We should celebrate with a day!
First-class senior magic knight.
I'm that much closer.
These four mages have to split...
Hold on!
Just a minute!
Man, I get a headache every time that guy opens his mouth.
Let's show some respect.
Although I don't disagree.
You do realize that's just as bad, right?
You fools fail to recognize the person whose achievements in the last battle were second to none!
The hero who guarded our kingdom's most precious treasure!
Hmm?
What about the great Seki-Brunsatsa?
Uh-huh!
Not only did you slugs have the audacity to leave your king unattended in a crisis, but certain parties were nasty enough to attack me as well!
I kind of wish I would have run him through!
Cool, shut up.
The glory belongs to Seki, not to them!
He's the real hero!
During that awful confrontation, he bravely dodged the enemy's spells and rushed to my rescue on that strange vehicle of his!
None of these other neophytes even attempted to help their king!
They should be punished, not praised!
Oh, honestly, I just kind of showed up.
By my authority as ruler of this kingdom,
I award to Seki the title of First Class Senior Magic Knight!
Did he say First Class Senior Magic Knight?
That's like the cream of the crop!
If that riff-raff is worthy of such prestige, then there's no reason I can't promote Seki to the same level!
Uh-oh.
Oh my god!
I've never felt this hated in my life!
They're gonna have my head!
Right.
It's a privilege to accept such an honor, your majesty.
I give you my word, I will fight!
And, uh, win!
No matter what!
I will always take great pride in protecting the Clover Kingdom with my very life,
and that's a promise!
So please don't kill me, okay?
Well then, will that be all, sir?
Yes!
I hope the rest of you will follow his example and always make me your utmost priority!
Forever!
Whew!
That was a close call!
Now, as I was saying, those five knights aside, everyone else who fought against the Eye of the Midnight Sun will be promoted by one rank.
I see. That must be why they asked all the captains to attend.
I knew that old blowhard being here wasn't a good enough reason to require us to come.
The Wizard King cares so deeply for our squads. I'm grateful.
All of the magic knights who risked their lives will be rewarded.
If not for the magic parliament trial causing all that chaos, there might have been many more promotions.
And although we cannot award them at this time, we've decided to give credit where we can.
Black Bull's Captain Yami Sukuhiro.
Really? I got something?
Please continue to exercise great leadership and help keep the Clover Kingdom peaceful.
I was kind of hoping for money, but thanks.
This concludes the special decoration ceremony.
In closing, I would like to read you a message from the Wizard King himself.
Although we have begun to recover from the previous conflict,
the threat of the Spade Kingdom looms ever nearer.
I expect nothing but the best from the knights who were promoted today.
To those who did not receive titles,
I trust that you will continue to train hard,
work together as magic knights,
and protect our beloved kingdom and all who reside here.
Yes, sir!
We're home!
You're never gonna catch me!
Shut up!
Quit moving around, you little punk!
You think the enemy's just gonna stand still and wait for you to hit him?
Oh, hey, it's Fineral and Captain Yami.
Welcome back, you guys.
Can't you runce train outside?
It's too damn loud.
Hey, look!
Uh-huh.
Now I got you.
We're gonna send you to the Heart Kingdom.
Really?
Does that mean it's official?
You and Nero, too, of course.
Plus, Noelle and my wheels here.
You're coming, too, Fineral?
It sure seems that way.
I can't wait till I kick some enemy butt!
Yep.
Go nuts, little fella.
Please.
Hm?
You have to let me go, too.
If he goes, I can't just sit here on my ass.
I promise I'll become even stronger than he is.
It was already decided in the Captain's meeting.
Sorry, Magna.
Please, boss.
I'm begging you here.
He's always a step ahead of me.
But if I'm going to be a real man, then I refuse to be left behind anymore.
I'll go even if you tell me to stay here.
With mana like yours, you're likely to get yourself killed.
You good with that?
Yes, sir.
I can push past the limits of my mana.
More than any commoner has before.
All right.
I'll ask Julius if there's room for another guy.
But just remember one thing.
It doesn't make a damn bit of difference where you train.
It's how that's important.
You understand?
Got it.
This is great.
I'm so happy you're coming with us.
It's real fun if I get too far ahead of you.
Yeah, watch out.
I'll catch up before you know it.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Sweet.
We got Finral, Magnus going, and luck.
Now let's head over to Heart and give it all we got!
Yeah!
Look at you, Karmy, to the top of the ladder in one step.
You really are the coolest guy ever!
I know you'll become the Wizard King soon.
Maybe sooner than we thought.
Don't be dumb.
It's not like it'll be that easy.
But yeah, someday.
It's only a matter of time.
I know you'll be that easy.
Like I can't inject gel подобного time.
Because I'd know you're coming with west.
I know you won't embarrass me yet.
You're so happy that I will guide you on the back.
Theéééééé Thoughts
I'll keep following my own path, and one day, I'll be the Wizard King.
Black Clover, page 154. Vice-Captain Longris Fod.
Don't hold back when you challenge me. You'll get hurt.